我真的没有信心可以为我们的家庭
I just don't ever see us being able to provide
创造一个安全可靠的未来
a secure future for our family.
我们刚刚在星城警用电台上发现了可疑的内容
Hey. We just got some strange chatter over the SCPD scanner.
有人报警说在市区的
Someone called in a bomb threat
一个综合购物大楼里发现炸弹威胁
at a shopping complex downtown.
这个人利用了信号跳转技术  无法追踪号码
Somebody using a signal-bounced untraceable number.
很可疑
Suspicious.
为什么惠美子要给她自己的袭击进行预警
Why would Emiko give an advance warning on her own attack?
这说不通
It doesn't make sense.
这样整座大楼里的人都会被疏散到外面的广场
So that the whole complex will evacuate into the plaza outside,
外面的广场才是她打算使用天鹅座的地方
where she'll deploy the Cygnus.
这样才能让伤亡最大化
Maximizing the casualty count.
我们决不能让这种事发生
Well, we can't let that happen.
我们一定能阻止她  我们走
We won't. Let's move out.